Hey y'all, we are open today from 3 to 8 PM,
as stated in the post.
We do not have cookies this weekend,
but we do have loaf cakes.
So here's the strawberry one.
It's a strawberry cake with buttercream frosting,
with our strawberry crunch.
We have the banana pudding one.
It has our buttercream frosting
with a banana flavored cake,
and then you also have banana pudding
on the top, with a vanilla wafer.
We have our Oreo one,
which is an Oreo cake with our Oreo buttercream,
with Oreo crumbles all on the top.
Then we have our Biscoff cookie butter one.
This is a cookie butter Biscoff flavored cake,
with cookie butter spread on the top
with some buttercream frosting.
And then we have our red velvet.
Okay, you already know about the red velvet.
Y'all come get this by Jay.
We do have these cakes this weekend.
We have all of the cups, all of the slices,
and then we have these cakes.